No.
[Dearest Episode 6]
Miss Wen, you're awake.
Why are you planning to leave
without a word?
I was afraid of waking you up.
Thank you for the clothes, Dr. Jiang.
I'll return them another day.
And thank you for saving me yesterday.
I'll contact Shang Yu
and let him send you
a gift to show my gratitude.
Is that all?
I remember yesterday that
you hugged and kissed me,
and said you wanted me to stay
by your side forever.
Now that the drug has worn off,
you're acting like a different one, huh?
Didn't you say, Dr. Jiang,
that after I sobered up,
I could do whatever I wanted?
Dr. Jiang,
you didn't take it seriously, did you?
no drug
requires
sex as an antidote.
If there is,
it must be that the woman
really wants to cling to you.
Am I right,
Alex?
You knew the truth?
I was wondering
why you understand women so well.
It turns out you're a professional.
No wonder Wen Xin thought
you looked familiar
the first time she saw you.
There’s absolutely no way you could
afford to live in the Clousea penthouse
by working as
a rehabilitation massage therapist.
You faked paralysis in the nursing home,
faked weakness in the Wen family,
and put on a pitiful act now.
You've been nominated
for Best Actress so many times.
How come you didn't win it?
Yes, I was acting.
We actors can do anything for a role.
What happened last night
was just a sacrifice for art.
Didn't you take it seriously, Dr. Jiang?
Your acting
is terrible.
I wasn't drawn into it at all.
Miss Wen,
you should improve your acting skills.
Dr. Jiang,
your acting isn't much better.
What kind of doctor would
wear perfume and style his hair like you?
Then, why are you keeping me around?
Don't you want to go back to Dad too,
my
dear brother?
What?
Are you scared?
Do you really think you're my brother?
Do you think I'm an idiot?
What exactly happened that night?
How did my mother die?
In the basement of
the Wen family's old house,
He Mu
picked up a Buddha statue.
Are you saying
my mother was killed by He Mu?
Yes.
I saw it with my own eyes.
You knew about this all along.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Aren't you doing this for revenge?
If I had told you then,
would you have believed me?
Or would you have thought
I was making up stories,
lying to you,
and shirking responsibility?
I kept you by my side
to let you see the truth
and gave you a chance for revenge.
Jiang Yu, you should thank me.
Wen Jianan,
you are taking advantage of me.
Jiang Yu,
aren't you doing the same?
Boss.
I found out. He...
He Mu got close to Councilman Qin
for the Xingji land deal.
Got it.
If he gets it,
he'll be the hero of
the Wen family's expansion.
But if he succeeds…
Then, we won't let him succeed.
He previously
misled me into thinking we were siblings,
using my hatred to take revenge on you.
Little did he know,
a pawn can also become a player.
I want him to be humiliated
and consumed by his own desires.
Then,
our cooperation begins.
It's a pleasure cooperating with you,
Miss Wen.
It was you
who framed my father.